<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MediConnect</string>
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">password</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="account_exists_click_here_to_login">Account Exists? Click Here To Login!</string>
    <string name="new_user_click_here">New User? Click Here!</string>
    <string name="logout">LOGOUT</string>
    <string name="mediconnect">MediConnect</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">home</string>
    <string name="logout_set">logout_set</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Privacy Policy for Storage App

\n Introduction
\n   Welcome to our Storage App. This Privacy Policy outlines how we collect, use, and protect your personal information when you use our app.
\n Information We Collect
\n   We may collect certain information when you use our app, including device information, location data, and user preferences.
\n Use of Information
\n   We use the collected information to provide and improve our services, personalize your experience, and communicate with you.
\n Data Security
\n   We implement appropriate security measures to protect your data against unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure.
\n Cookies and Tracking
\n   Our app may use cookies and similar tracking technologies to enhance user experience and analyze usage patterns.
\n Third-Party Services
\n   We may use third-party services that have their own privacy policies. We encourage you to review their policies.
\n Data Sharing
\n   We do not sell or share your personal information with third parties except as necessary to provide our services.
\n Data Retention
\n   We retain your information only as long as necessary for the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy.
\n Children's Privacy
\n   Our app is not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children.
\n User Rights
\n    You have the right to access, correct, or delete your personal information. Contact us for assistance.
\n Opt-Out
\n    You can opt out of certain data collection and processing by adjusting settings within the app.
\n Changes to Policy
\n    We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Check back periodically for any changes.
\n Consent
\n    By using our app, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
n Location Services
\n    Our app may request access to your device's location to provide location-based features. You can manage location settings in your device's settings.
\n Analytics
\n    We use analytics tools to gather and analyze app usage data for improving our services.
\n Advertising
\n    Our app may display third-party advertisements. Ad providers may collect data for ad personalization.
\n Account Information
\n    If you create an account, we may store and use your account information to provide personalized services.
\n Data Transfer
\n    Your information may be transferred to and stored on servers located in different countries for processing.

\n Contact Information
\n   If you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at rishirpoojary.com.

\n Effective Date
\n    This Privacy Policy is effective as of  13 April 2024.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="wishuser">wishuser</string>
    <string name="logoutfromhere">logoutfromhere</string>
    <string name="read_more">Read More</string>

</resources>